russiawomendate.com 2014-06-17

# Russian Dating Service for Singles to Meet Russian Women, Ukrainian Girls. - RussiawomenDate.com

**Personal Privacy and Data Disposal Policy**

The RussiawomenDate Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use RussiawomenDate subsidiary sites' services ("Services"), including information provided when you use RussiawomenDate.com. The following describes our privacy practices that are specific to RussiawomenDate.com.

Welcome to RussiawomenDate.com ("RussiawomenDate" or the "Site"). Your privacy is important to us. As such, we provide this Policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected, processed, maintained and disposed by RussiawomenDate, including any services owned, operated or offered by or on behalf of RussiawomenDate, and by third-party service providers if applicable.

We understand that the privacy of our members, subscribers, guests and/or visitors ("Members", "you" or "your") is very important. We have developed this Policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using RussiawomenDate. We reserve the right to change it at any time, and all changes are effective upon posting with notice to you.

Owing to the global nature of RussiawomenDate's business conducted over the internet, it is practically impossible for us to comply with all applicable laws / rules / regulations (and the like) as may be prescribed by individual country / region / city. We endeavor to adopt internationally recommended “Best Practices” whilst adhering to the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, laws of Hong Kong which you must agree to as the applicable law in case of dispute arising herefrom.

Operationally we are in compliance with, though not bound to do so, the general requirements imposed by the Data Protection Principles generally recommended by the US-EU US-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks, Organisation for Economic Cooperation & Development, and by the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation. In particular, we carry out Privacy Compliance Assessment exercise periodically to ensure compliance in respect of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement.

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of RussiawomenDate. In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy policy to describe how RussiawomenDate processes personal information. Please review and agree to those Supplementary Privacy Policy.

1\. About RussiawomenDate and Your Information We Collect

RussiawomenDate provides you with access to rich collection of resources, including without limitation various communication tools, products, contents, software, forums, services through its network of web sites (collectively "Services"). In order to provide a full range of services, we may ask you to create a RussiawomenDate Account (the “Account”) to be our member. In the course of these various offerings, we often seek to collect from you various forms of personal information. We may ask you to create a Personal Profile and it generally includes three sets of information :

a) Personal Data

This includes your personal data such as your gender, first, middle and last names, date of birth and ethnicity. This information may be accessed and viewed by others, as determined by your agreement on the specific privacy practices with respect to certain Services.

b) Additional Information

You may elect to include your additional information, such as your height, weight, smoker or not, alcoholic or not, native / spoken language(s), education level, religion, profession, whether have children or not, current income range, your marital status, your ideal match age range. You may also include other content, such as a narrative description of yourself and photo(s). This information is stored on our systems, and may be displayed in your public profile on RussiawomenDate, or included in any communication between Members sent via RussiawomenDate and other RussiawomenDate Sites.

c) Contact Information

It consists of your email address, your postal address such as street address, city, state/province, residence country as well as postal code. Your telephone or fax number are required when filling in the registration form. Contact information will not be shown on your profile or other public places.

2\. How We Use Your Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our Services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you other products or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to enforce the legal obligations that govern your use of our Site, to identify problems, to resolve complaint, disputes and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information.

You agree that we may use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze the web site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize RussiawomenDate's content, layout, and services. These uses can help us improve our Site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

3\. Cookies and Historical Information

Each time you access the Services, various information is gathered automatically, such as: domain, computer platform, browser type, IP address and place of origin. We gather this information in order to administer and optimize the Services for you and to diagnose problems with our Services and enhance your user experience.

4\. Your Card Details

If you pay by card online, to protect your privacy we engage highly secured industry order processing provided by third-party billing companies such as PayPal. Those companies we cooperate enjoy good reputation and reliability in the industry of its kind. With use of the third-party card processors, your card information is processed through secure server(s), and transferred internally with the protection of powerful encryption tool available. Your customer details will not be sold or made available to anyone else and your card details are only known by our order processors.

5\. Communications

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other RussiawomenDate members or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on RussiawomenDate, we may collect such information that is accessed only by authorized RussiawomenDate personnel or representatives. We may also collect other members' comments about you.

6\. Our Disclosure and/or Shared Use of Your Information

Under no circumstance will RussiawomenDate sell or transfer for monetary gains your information to any unrelated third party without your permission, but we may disclose your information to affiliates or unaffiliated third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government administrative request or other due process; (b) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of RussiawomenDate or others; (c) to enforce any terms of service of RussiawomenDate; (d) to provide you with the services or products requested by you, and to perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; (e) to provide you with information, special offers, or promotions from RussiawomenDate to which you consented. RussiawomenDate makes reasonable efforts to limit its designated service providers' disclosure of your information in the same manner as set forth in this paragraph.

Further use and/or disclosure of your information by third parties is not the responsibility of RussiawomenDate. Rather, such use and/or disclosure is governed by those parties’ policies.

As your RussiawomenDate Account is inter-linked with all our member sites (which means you can activate multiple memberships on those sites when you successfully obtain an Account), we may also share your information with those Sites when they are interested in serving you. You may notify us of your membership preferences any time in our member account settings area. Unless and until you choose to opt-out your membership on RussiawomenDate, your information may be used by RussiawomenDate for providing goods and services to you.

7\. Updating Your Information

If you want to update or correct inaccuracies in your information, you can login to your account and modify it any time on your own initiative. In the unlikely event of certain information items you do not manage to update through our system, please contact our Customer Support Team for assistance.

8\. Deleting Your Account

Gentleman members can reqire account deletion through submitting email request to our customer service team, specifying whether account deletion of RussiawomenDate or account deletion of the RussiawomenDate is needed. When RussiawomenDate account is deleted, members will not be able to log into RussiawomenDate and/or check usage history. When the RussiawomenDate account is deleted, members will not be able to log into all member sites under RussiawomenDate and use our Services any more.

9\. Technical and/or Operational Security

We respect and recognize that personal data are vulnerable to security breach which, if taken place, may cause annoyance or even damages to you (conversely, our business reputation), thus we take reasonably practical measures to protect your personal data. However, given the realistic limitations (e.g. costs / timely delivery of security measures) and rapid revolution of technology, there is always the risk of such breach in which event we cannot be held liable.

RussiawomenDate has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identity information such as encryption tools, secure server and firewall. While "absolutely fail-safe security" does not exist, our technical experts work hard to ensure your secure use of our services.

10\. Cross-border Transfer of Personal Information

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Policy may involve the transfer of your information to various areas around the world that may have levels of privacy protection different from that of your residence country. By submitting your information via RussiawomenDate, you consent to such cross-border transfers notwithstanding the restrictions imposed by applicable law / rule / regulation to the contrary.

11\. Links To Third-Party Websites

RussiawomenDate may provide links to third-party websites. Since we do not control third-party sites and are not responsible for any information you may provide while on such sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those web sites before providing any of your personal information on such sites.

12\. Your Agreement to This Policy

By using RussiawomenDate Services, you understand that this Policy applies solely to information collected by RussiawomenDate, and you agree to the collection, processing, retention and disposal of your information by RussiawomenDate as outlined herein.
